libapps.com 2014-06-25

# Springshare's LibApps Privacy Policy

Here is the privacy policy wrapped in the legal language, to satisfy the inner lawyer in all of us (and to satisfy our lawyers, too). 

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Springshare LLC collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of Springshare's web applications ("Apps"). 

**Personally identifiable information**  
We may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our Apps, register on the Apps, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Apps. We will collect personally identifiable information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us or, in case of phone numbers, if they use the SMS portion of our Apps. Users can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Apps related activities. 

**Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Apps. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users' means of connection to our Apps, such as the operating system, IP address and other similar information. 

**Web browser cookies**  
Our Apps use "cookies" to enhance User experience. The Users' web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. Users may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to be alerted when cookies are being sent. If they do so, some parts of the Apps may not function properly. 

**How we use collected information**  
Springshare LLC collects and uses Users' personal information for the following purposes:

  * To enable the use of our Apps. Certain portions of Springshare's Apps require User registration, i.e. the use of email and other personal information.
  * To personalize the Users' experience. We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided by our Apps.
  * To send periodic emails and news updates only to registered users of Springshare's Apps. The email address Users provide will only be used to send them information and updates pertaining to their use of the Apps. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How we protect your information**  
We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored in our Apps. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of the information you transmit to us, so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. 

**Sharing your personal information**  
We do not sell, trade, or rent Users' personally identifiable information to others. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Apps or administer activities on our behalf. We may share your email address with these third parties for those limited purposes and those third parties are restricted in the use of your information. By deleting their accounts in our Apps, Users can always opt out of this communication. We will disclose Users' personal information if we believe in good faith that it is required by law, or to protect public safety. 

**Third party websites**  
Our Apps contain links to other sites, which may contain advertising and other content. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by websites linked to or from our Apps. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**  
Springshare LLC may update this Privacy Policy at any time. When we do, we will post the changes here. This Privacy Policy was updated last on February 9, 2011 

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us at [info@springshare.com](mailto:info@springshare.com).
